[
  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "1.",
    "answer" : "Innere Stadt"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "2.",
    "answer" : "Leopoldstadt"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "3.",
    "answer" : "Landstraße"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "4.",
    "answer" : "Wieden"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "5.",
    "answer" : "Margarethen"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "6.",
    "answer" : "Mariahilf"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "7.",
    "answer" : "Neubau"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "8.",
    "answer" : "Josefstadt"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "9.",
    "answer" : "Alsergrund"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "10.",
    "answer" : "Favoriten"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "11.",
    "answer" : "Simmering"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "12.",
    "answer" : "Meidling"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "13.",
    "answer" : "Hietzing"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "14.",
    "answer" : "Penzing"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "15.",
    "answer" : "Rudolfsheim Fünfhaus"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "16.",
    "answer" : "Ottakring"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "17.",
    "answer" : "Hernals"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "18.",
    "answer" : "Währing"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "19.",
    "answer" : "Döbling"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "20.",
    "answer" : "Brigittenau"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "21.",
    "answer" : "Floridsdorf"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "22.",
    "answer" : "Donaustadt"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Bezirke Wien",
    "question" : "23.",
    "answer" : "Liesing"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Griechisch für den Urlaub",
    "question" : "Guten Morgen!",
    "answer" : "Kali mera!"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Griechisch für den Urlaub",
    "question" : "Guten Abend!",
    "answer" : "Kali spéra"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Griechisch für den Urlaub",
    "question" : "Danke!",
    "answer" : "Efcharistó!"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Griechisch für den Urlaub",
    "question" : "Guten Tag!",
    "answer" : "Yassas!"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Griechisch für den Urlaub",
    "question" : "bitte",
    "answer" : "paracalló"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English classroom vocabulary",
    "question" : "Tafel",
    "answer" : "board"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English classroom vocabulary",
    "question" : "Bleistift",
    "answer" : "pencil"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English classroom vocabulary",
    "question" : "Buch, Heft",
    "answer" : "book"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English classroom vocabulary",
    "question" : "Sessel",
    "answer" : "chair"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English classroom vocabulary",
    "question" : "Schreibtisch",
    "answer" : "desk"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English classroom vocabulary",
    "question" : "Schultasche",
    "answer" : "schoolbag"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Oberarmknochen",
    "answer" : "Humerus"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Schlüsselbein",
    "answer" : "Clavicula"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Schulterblatt",
    "answer" : "Scapula"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Speiche",
    "answer" : "Radius"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Elle",
    "answer" : "Ulna"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Handwurzelknochen",
    "answer" : "Ossa carpi"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Mittelhandknochen",
    "answer" : "Ossa metacarpalia"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Knochen Deutsch-Latein",
    "question" : "Fingerknochen",
    "answer" : "Phalanges digitorum manus"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Heilpflanzen Deutsch - Latein",
    "question" : "Augentrost",
    "answer" : "Euphrasia rostkovina"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Heilpflanzen Deutsch - Latein",
    "question" : "Baldrian",
    "answer" : "Valerian"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Heilpflanzen Deutsch - Latein",
    "question" : "Brennnessel",
    "answer" : "Urtica"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Heilpflanzen Deutsch - Latein",
    "question" : "Rosmarin",
    "answer" : "Salvia rosmarinus"
  },

  {
    "box" : "Heilpflanzen Deutsch - Latein",
    "question" : "Salbei",
    "answer" : "Salvia"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English irregular plurals",
    "question" : "mouse",
    "answer" : "mice"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English irregular plurals",
    "question" : "louse",
    "answer" : "lice"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English irregular plurals",
    "question" : "fish",
    "answer" : "fish"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English irregular plurals",
    "question" : "foot",
    "answer" : "feet"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English irregular plurals",
    "question" : "tooth",
    "answer" : "teeth"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English irregular plurals",
    "question" : "child",
    "answer" : "children"
  },

  {
    "box" : "English irregular plurals",
    "question" : "person",
    "answer" : "people"
  }
]